areyouami.com 2019-06-16

# Security & Privacy - Are You Am I

**Safe and Secure Shopping**

We know that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our privacy policy. **By visiting areyouami.com, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.**

**What personal information does Are You Am I gather about its customers?**

Information That You Provide: We receive and store any information that a customer enters on our website or gives us in any way. This information is used to enhance your experience on our website, to respond to your requests, to customize your shopping experience and to communicate with you.

Automatic Information: Some information is received and stored automatically whenever you interact with us. "Cookies" are one example of this type of information. In internet terms, a "cookie" is a text file that websites send to visiting computers/devices to identify the visiting computer/device. We also may use third-party website analytics tools. These tools collect information about visitor traffic on our website and mobile applications.

Information from Other Sources: We might also receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information. All information gathered is for the sole purpose of personalizing and improving your user experience.

**How does Are You Am I use your contact informations?**

We use your contact information for the following purposes only:

    * Register you as a user on our website;
    * Manage and/or maintain your user account and wish list on our website;
    * Process and deliver purchases, returns, backorders etc;
    * Communicate with you and provide customer support;
    * Let you know about products, promotions and events that might be of special interest to you;

If for some reason you would prefer not to receive emails from Are You Am I simply email a request to [support@areyouami.com](mailto:support@areyouami.com) with the word "UNSUBSCRIBE" in the subject line. Please note that any requests to remove or update your contact information may take seven to ten working days to take effect.

**How do we use your other customer information?**

    * Customize our services and product offerings to suit your needs and interests;
    * Record purchases that you have made on our website;
    * Let you communicate with us through social networks and other media;
    * Allow you to post comments on our website, on social networks and other media;
    * Detect fraud and unauthorized transactions, including identifying potential unauthorized users and/or hackers;
    * Enforce our Terms of Use;
    * Comply with applicable legal requirements, industry standards and our policies.

**Does Are You Am I share customer information?**

Your privacy is always respected when you shop with Are You Am I. From time to time we might establish business relationships with other persons or entities whom we believe trustworthy and whom we have asked to confirm that their privacy policies are consistent with ours.

Your customer information may be shared with such carefully selected partners in order to enhance your shopping experience. We also sometimes allow third-party companies to collect certain anonymous information (e.g. mouse clicks, mouse movements, scroll behavior and/or keystroke activity) during your visits in order to further enhance your shopping experience.

_Notice to California Residents: If you are a California resident,[California Civil Code Section 1798.83](http://www.leginfo.ca.gov/cgi-bin/displaycode?section=civ&group=01001-02000&file=1798.80-1798.84 "California Civil Code Section 1798.83") permits you to request information regarding the disclosure of your personal information by Are You Am I to any third parties, including (i) a list of the categories of personal information about you that Are You Am I has disclosed to third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes during the calendar year preceding your request, (ii) the names and addresses of such third parties, and (iii) if the nature of the third parties’ business cannot reasonably be determined from their names, examples of the products or services marketed sufficient to give you a reasonable indication of the nature of the third parties' business. To submit a request with the subject heading "CALIFORNIA PRIVACY REQUEST" to_[ _support@areyouami.com_](mailto:support@areyouami.com) _._

**How secure is my customer information?**

All transactions submitted to us are encrypted with 128 SSL software which encrypts information you input to protect it from interception by outside parties. Are You Am I is committed to maintaining the highest levels of security and protection against fraud. We stay up-to-date with the latest in security technologies to ensure that your credit card information, contact information and shipping/billing information are confidential and safe. Unfortunately, however, no data transmission over the internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your contact information, to the extent permitted by law, we do not guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit to or from our websites, you do so at your own risk.

**What choices do I have?**

As discussed above, you may choose not to provide information, even though it might be needed to make a purchase or to take advantage of certain Are You Am I features. If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us or if you have any questions about how your information is being used, please simply send a request to support@areyouami.com

**Are children allowed to use areyouami.com?**

Are You Am I does not sell products for purchase by children. If you are under 18, you may use Are You Am I only with the authorization and involvement of a parent or guardian.

**Conditions of use, notices, and revisions**

If you choose to visit Are You Am I, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Policy and our Terms of Use. If you have any concern about privacy at Are You Am I please contact us at [support@areyouami.com](mailto:supprt@areyouami.com) with a description of your concern, and we will try to resolve it. Our Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use for Are You Am I are subject to change without notice. Such changes will go into effect on the date that the notice is posted, will apply to all current and past users of our website and will replace any prior policies that are inconsistent. Your continued use of our website or other services constitutes your acceptance of the practices described in the revised Privacy Policy and Terms of Use.

1/1/2016 version
